<Tutorial>
	<Message id="ALPHA WORK1">Your design has now been promoted to implementation.

The implementation phase has three stages:

1. "Alpha", in which developers and artists create the product according to the design specifications and requirements.

2. "Delay", depending on how competent your employees are, unexpected issues may crop up during alpha, which need to be addressed before moving on.

3. "Beta", in which bugs are uncovered by your programmers and hopefully fixed before the final release.

Press "Promote" in the action menu when the alpha is ready. Note that you will lose some quality if you end the alpha phase prematurily, but it might also be the best thing to do if you want beat a competitor to the punch or you are running out of money.

The tutorial will continue once you begin the delay phase.</Message>
	<Message id="ALPHA WORK2">Your alpha has entered a delay phase, in which employees scramble to finish up the alpha.

Press "Beta" to skip this stage or wait for the delay to finish and promote to beta automatically.

Note that prematurely promoting to beta will add extra bugs, which might take longer to fix than the delay phase takes to finish.

The tutorial will continue once you begin the beta phase.</Message>
	<Message id="ALPHA WORK3">Bugs are now being fixed. The amount of bugs that can be fixed depends on the competence of your employees.
	
Even the best programmer may not uncover all bugs and you'll have to deal with them after release by responding to customer support tickets.

Press "Release" when you are ready.

Press "End" to finish the tutorial.</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE1">按下“建造”按钮打开“建造模式”来开始。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE2">在“建造模式”中，游戏将会暂停。

让我们先来建造一个房间。您将有两种方法来建造一个房间。

您可以点击“建造矩形房间”按钮来建造一个标准的矩形房间或点击“建造房间”按钮来建造墙面，从而建造任意形状的房间。

您也可以在“建造房间”时把一个房间分为两个。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE3">您可以在由方格标出的土地上兴建您的房间。请注意房间建造的成本。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE4">您可能注意到了您建造房间时受到了方格的限制。您可以通过这些选项来更改方格的设置从而建造更加复杂的多边形。当您打算靠着一堵斜角墙放置家具时，调整这些选项将十分有用。

当准备好继续后点击“继续”按钮。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE5">您可以用Q和E在上、下楼层间切换。

现在我们来添加门和窗户把。您可以在类别中筛选门和窗户或直接在搜索框中搜索他们。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE6">当您放置窗户时，您的房间也将变得明亮。请保证您的房间拥有足够的窗户来让您的员工不至于抹黑办公。

通过选择房间，您可以查看房间的环境、光照、温度和噪声情况。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE7">您也可以改变房间和家具的颜色。

请尝试在房间上点击右键，选择图标为一个画笔的“房间颜色”按钮。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE8">在打开上色面板前，您可以通过按住Shift并点击多个物品来同时改变他们的颜色。上色面板会默认显示他们当前的颜色。

如果您很喜欢您设计的这个房间的颜色，您可以在右键菜单中把它设置为默认设置。

若要应用颜色设置，点击“应用”按钮。若想取消颜色设置，请直接关闭上色面板。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE9">让我们给房间放点新家具吧。

点击“装修”按钮或搜索“table”来为房间添加一张桌子。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE10">现在，添加一个椅子。椅子只能放在桌子边上。

注意，拥有多个层次的家具，比如椅子，能够进行升级。您能够在房子的右键菜单中选择“所有家具”来选择房间中的所有家具，并在右键菜单中一次性升级所有家具。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE11">最后，添加一台电脑。按住左键并拖曳可以调整电脑的朝向。

电脑必须放在桌子上并朝向一个椅子。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE12">当你把多张桌子放到一起（桌子上不能有东西）时，这些桌子会组合起来。组合起来的桌子很适合作为会议桌。要查看组合的桌子，选中一个桌子，与之组合的桌子会以蓝色标出。

点击“继续”按钮以继续。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE13">您自己的角色不会觉得累、饿、冷、需要去厕所等。但是你的其他员工会有这些需求。因此在您雇佣新员工前请保证公司内至少由一个冰箱、一个咖啡机、一个暖气、一个换气扇和一个隔开的厕所。

点击“继续”按钮以继续。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE14">现在，让我们把这个房间分配给一个小组。房间被分配给某个小组后，其他小组的员工就不会进入这个房间了。

右键点击您的房间并选择“切换小组”。在打开的窗口内选择“核心”来把这个房间分配给核心小组。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE15">记住给把员工分配给小组。 您可以右键点击员工并选择“切换小组”或在员工管理页面更改员工小组。当公司内只有一个小组时，所有员工都会被自动分配到该小组。

按住Shift并能让你一次选中多个物品、房间和员工。选中后您可以在任意地方右键点击来打开动作菜单。

请尝试选中至少两件物品。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE16">如果您想合并两个房间，请按住Shift并选中您想合并的房间，右键点击并在动作菜单中选择“合并房间”。

现在，让我们退出“建造模式”。</Message>
	<Message id="BUILD MODE17">当你准备好后，请点击员工管理来开始管理你的员工。</Message>
	<Message id="CONTRACTS1">打开“工作合同”窗口来开始。</Message>
	<Message id="CONTRACTS2">这里列举了所有的合同。新合同将会在现有合同被完成后添加。

每个合同将会有先期付款，先期付款将在您接下合同时付给您。而当您完成合同后会收到尾款。若您未完成合同或软件出现了未修复的Bug，您将会被罚款。低于要求的质量或超过时间都会导致最终收入减少。

浏览并选择一个您认为可以接收的合同吧！</Message>
	<Message id="CUSTOMIZATION1">欢迎来到捏人页面。按下“继续”来继续教程或按下“取消”来关闭教程。</Message>
	<Message id="CUSTOMIZATION2">请给你的公司取个名字。</Message>
	<Message id="CUSTOMIZATION3">接下来给你的公司元老取个名字。</Message>
	<Message id="CUSTOMIZATION4">选择一个性别。</Message>
	<Message id="CUSTOMIZATION5">通过这些选项你能更改角色的外貌和着装。
	
</Message>
	<Message id="CUSTOMIZATION7">在这里您可以选择角色的个性。

您可以选择两个个性，个性将会影响角色的行为（领导力、学习能力和懒惰程度）和人际关系</Message>
	<Message id="CUSTOMIZATION8">在这里您可以选择角色的能力值和专长，它们将影响角色的工作表现。

专长将受到能力值的限制。这意味着如果您的角色的设计能力十分低下，他/她在设计领域里专长的方面的设计能力一样会很低下。

在游戏中您可以通过教育让您的角色获得新的能力值和专长。</Message>
	<Message id="CUSTOMIZATION9">您的角色已经准备好了！现在让我们来看看游戏的规则设定吧！</Message>
	<Message id="CUSTOMIZATION10">您可以在这里开启Mod。Mod设置将不能在游戏进行时更改。

您可以把您的游戏分享给其他人，即使他们没有安装这些Mod。

有的Mod会增加新的场景，因此您应该在选择场景前开启这些Mod。</Message>
	<Message id="CUSTOMIZATION11">现在请选择一个场景。场景将会影响您能选择的起始金钱和起始日期、目标和竞争者的模拟方式。</Message>
	<Message id="CUSTOMIZATION12">您可以在这里更改环境。

森林是默认环境，冻土全年都很冷，沙漠全年都很热而城市有预制的一栋摩天大楼、道路和停车场。</Message>
	<Message id="CUSTOMIZATION13">您可以在选项中随时更改难度。难度将会影响员工的工资和效率，并影响竞争者的竞争力。</Message>
	<Message id="CUSTOMIZATION14">一般来说在游戏中1天就是一个月。这将保持游戏的节奏从而不会让玩家觉得太无聊。

若您觉得游戏节奏太快或您需要更多的时间来赚钱并使得工资的结算更晚一些，您可以增加每月的天数。

请注意，游戏中的事件的出现和发生会随着您的设置而变慢。您将不能在游戏进行时更改这个设置。</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT1">按下“开发软件”按钮来开始软件开发的教程。</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT2">欢迎来到软件设计，这是这个游戏的核心。

选择一个软件类型来开始。

点击“继续”来继续</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT3">If applicable, you can pick a software category. Each category for a software type has different development times, popularity, audience retention, features and it's own target audience.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT4">Then pick a name. You can either write one yourself or press the "Name:" button to have it generated.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT5">You can also pick a price. If you leave the price field alone, the best price will be picked based on the software and features you've chosen. You can click the Price button to reset the price.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT6">Now you must pick features for your product. Each feature takes time to develop and balances innovation, stability and usability, so pick carefully.

The features you can pick depend on which software dependencies and operating systems you chose. When you select features, dependencies and operating systems will be filtered accordingly, this also works the other way around.

Some features are artistic in nature and you will need artists on the team to get the best result.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT7">You can use these buttons to quickly select features. Note that it might not always be best to just select all features.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT8">Your product can depend on other software types. As an example, you will need a visual tool, like an image editor, to make a game with 2D graphics or you won't be able to make the graphics for it.

The features you pick will determine what type of software you need to develop your product and the quality of the dependencies will affect the quality of your product.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT9">Pick a software you want to use from the list by selecting it and pressing "OK".

You can filter software by features, the features you can pick for your software will sometimes depend on the features of the software you pick here.

Take special note of quality and license costs. Your software's quality will depend on the quality of the software you pick and you will have to pay the license fees.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT10">Some software runs on an operating system and some software can only run on operating systems that the software it is built on can run on, e.g. Games can only run on the operating systems that its Game Engine can run on. And as before, your features might also depend on which operating systems you choose to support.

You can pick your operating systems here. If nothing is shown, the software type you picked is not operating system dependent.

Press "Continue" to carry on.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT11">You can make your software a sequel to a product you made previously or which you have bought from another company. You do this by clicking this button and selecting a product as you did with operating systems and software needs.

Making a sequel will give a marketing boost and change your fans' expectations depending on the success of its predecessors.

Features that were implemented for the predecessor will be highlighted in orange in the feature panel, these features will be developed faster when you develop your product.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT12">You can also make your software in-house, which means you won't sell it to other companies.

You can use this to develop top quality game engines and only use them for your own games, to gain an advantage over other companies.

If this is not visible, it means the software you picked is meant for an audience and it wouldn't make sense to keep it in-house.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT13">If your software depends on server functionality, like an MMO, you will need to pick a server from this list.

If your servers cannot handle the load this software will generate, they will quickly burn out and you will lose your reputation.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT14">Finally, you can pick a source control server from this list to support the development.

Using source control will decrease bugs and speed up development, if your server can handle the load.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT15">After you've went through the phases of development and you're ready to release your product, remember to see if any popular products has just been released in the same software category as yours.

You can also check out upcoming releases from your competitors to make sure a large company won't outshine your product.

Timing is everything when you're just starting out!</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN DOCUMENT16">Before you finish, make sure you inspect the information in this box. This outlines everything you need to develop this product.

Take special note of consumer reach. Consumer reach is how many people can potentially purchase the product as of right now, this number might decrease or increase as you develop the product. For software that depend on operating systems, it will be limited by how many people are currently using the operating system and it's successors.

Having more than the suggested amount of employees on the development teams will not increase development speed, but might actually reduce it instead.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN WORK1">To start developing your software, designers need to piece together a document, which describes how the software should be developed and structured, to make sure everyone is on the same page.
	
Design work items are worked on by designers or employees in "Any role" until you promote the work item to alpha.

Press "continue" to advance the tutorial.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN WORK2">Begin by assigning the work item to a team, if you haven't already. Hover over the bottom area of the work item to bring up the action menu and select "Assign".

You can also unassign teams to pause work.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN WORK3">Now employees on the team you have assigned will begin work, if they have a computer to sit at.

The work item will slowly fill up as it progresses. For design documents it is important to stop when the task is completely green, so you don't lose quality. If you wait too long, inexperienced designers will begin over-engineering.</Message>
	<Message id="DESIGN WORK4">You can click the clock icon to start a mini game, which will add extra quality to the design, but time is fast forwarded while you play.

You can use mini games to speed work along, but you should only use this in the starting phases of your company, as the quality addition does not scale with project complexity and you will have other things to attend to later on.

Click "Develop" in the Action menu when the progress bar is filled to begin alpha development.

Right click the title bar to collapse the work item.

Left click the title bar to re-arrange your work items.

Click "End" to finish the tutorial.

Click buttons to improve life.</Message>
	<Message id="DISTRIBUTION1">Begin the distribution tutorial by opening the distribution window</Message>
	<Message id="DISTRIBUTION2">In order to sell your products, you need distributors to give them to customers.

There are two types of distribution channels, online and physcial stores. Online stores sell your products for a cut of the revenue, whereas physical stores require upfront payment for producing physical copies, but they also boost your product's marketing.

When you start a new game you are already publishing through all online distributors. You can see which distributors you are using by looking at the Active column.

Press continue to advance the tutorial.</Message>
	<Message id="DISTRIBUTION3">You also have the option of opening your own distribution channel, which other companies can make use of.

Note that this requires a robust server farm or people will get angry with your company.

Press End to finish the tutorial.</Message>
	<Message id="EDUCATION1">Begin the tutorial by selecting one or more of your employees, right click anywhere on the screen to bring up the action menu, and then pick "Educate".</Message>
	<Message id="EDUCATION2">This is the education window. You can use education to make your employee better at their jobs or enable responsibilities for your leaders.

You can choose to either educate your employee in a skill, specialization or you can enable HR or project management by checking one of the options in the bottom of the education window.</Message>
	<Message id="EDUCATION3">Start by choosing the amount of months to educate your employees. Note that educational courses are considered paid leave, so you will also be paying salaries on top of course expenses.

There is a limit to the skills and specializations of your employees, so if you pick 3 months of courses for an employee with a high skilll level, you'll be throwing money out the window.</Message>
	<Message id="EDUCATION4">Then pick what role you want to educate your employees in.</Message>
	<Message id="EDUCATION5">If you picked Designer, Programmer or Artist, you should pick what specialization you want them to improve in. Click "Start education" when you are ready to send your employee off.</Message>
	<Message id="EMPLOYEES1">打开员工管理页面以开始</Message>
	<Message id="EMPLOYEES2">这里列举了您所有的员工以及他们的状态。

通过这些选项您可以设定列表中现实的信息。</Message>
	<Message id="EMPLOYEES3">当您在列表中选中一名员工时，他们也会在游戏中被选中，您可以在窗口下方查看他们的专长。

现在请试试选中一名员工吧。</Message>
	<Message id="EMPLOYEES4">按住Shift可以同时选中多名员工。

现在，在任意地方点击右键来打开该员工的“动作菜单”。选择“切换小队”并在打开的菜单中选择中“Core”来把该员工分配到“Core”小队。</Message>
	<Message id="EMPLOYEES5">现在，在任意地方右键点击打开“动作菜单”，选择“更改员工角色”。</Message>
	<Message id="EMPLOYEES6">在“更改角色”窗口中点击角色将为员工指定角色。您也可以选择“任意角色”来让该员工可以作为任意角色。

请注意，除非员工被分配到某个组里，否则员工不能被指定为“领导”。而属于“任意角色”的员工不能作为组内领导。

关闭“更改角色”窗口并点击“继续”来继续教程。</Message>
	<Message id="EMPLOYEES7">当选中员工时，在任意位置点击右键打开“动作菜单”并选择“员工详情”。</Message>
	<Message id="EMPLOYEES8">您可以在这里查看员工的状态。

在左上方您可以看到您员工的特点。在特点下面是您员工在各种角色的能力值。点击一个角色将会把该员工分配到该角色。</Message>
	<Message id="EMPLOYEES9">在左下角您可以查看员工的专长。您也可以通过这里看出您员工的受教育程度。
	
“基础能力”是您员工在这些方面的总体能力。</Message>
	<Message id="EMPLOYEES10">在右上角是员工的特点，这些特点由员工的两个个性控制。

您可以把鼠标悬浮在各个特点上查看它们对员工的影响。</Message>
	<Message id="EMPLOYEES11">在右边中央的位置会显示员工最近的想法。这些想法将告诉你这名员工对当前工作环境的满意程度。</Message>
	<Message id="EMPLOYEES12">最后，在窗口右下角，您可以查看当前有什么在影响员工的工作。
	
若您的员工突然开始消极怠工，您可以在这里查看发生了什么问题。</Message>
	<Message id="EMPLOYEES13">在游戏开始时你需要快速地赚一些钱。

打开“工作合同”窗口来接点工作吧！</Message>
	<Message id="HIRING1">Start by opening the hire window</Message>
	<Message id="HIRING2">Before you can hire anyone, you need to put out a search for employees. Start by choosing which role your new employee should be good at.</Message>
	<Message id="HIRING3">If you've picked a programmer, artist or designer, you should also pick a specialization you want them to be good at.</Message>
	<Message id="HIRING4">Then you need to decide how much money you want to give your potential employee per month. It is very important that you make sure you have enough money to actually pay them or you'll go bankrupt very quickly.

The quality of applicants will depend on how high you set the salary and the reputation of your company.</Message>
	<Message id="HIRING5">You can also choose to interview employees in specific areas upfront. You can wait to interview employees before you hire them, but that might be more expensive, depending on how many you intend to hire.

Each interview option will double the search price.</Message>
	<Message id="HIRING6">Finally, you need to decide how much money you want to spend searching for applicants. The more money you spend, the more potential employees you will reach. You're guaranteed to receive at least one application.

Press "Begin looking" to begin searching.</Message>
	<Message id="HIRING7">This is a list of employees that applied to the open position in your company.</Message>
	<Message id="HIRING8">You can select employees to inspect them and press the "Hire" button to hire them. Employees are expensive and you should probably wait before you hire any if you are just starting out.

Try selecting an employee on the list.</Message>
	<Message id="HIRING9">You can easily navigate the applications by using the arrow keys on your keyboard and pressing enter to hire.

When you are done, simply close the window.</Message>
	<Message id="HR1">To enable HR management open the team window</Message>
	<Message id="HR2">With the team window open, scroll the team list all the way to the right and click "Automation" in the list, on the team you wish to enable HR for.</Message>
	<Message id="HR3">Go over the HR settings and check "Enable HR management" when you are done. The Budget might need to be increased once in a while, so good employees don't seek out new job opportunities.

Close the automation window to finish this tutorial.</Message>
	<Message id="INSURANCE1">Start by opening the insurance window</Message>
	<Message id="INSURANCE2">You can deposit and withdraw money by using this slider.

Money on your insurance account earns you 5% interest per year (up to a certain amount), so it's a great place to keep money.

Withdrawing and depositing money in the insurance account affects your employee's satisfaction based on their age, so be careful when you withdraw money.</Message>
	<Message id="INSURANCE3">Employees retire, or might die or get sick. When this happens they will receive money from your insurance account, so there is some risk involved in depositing money into this account.

You can keep up with what payments have been made in this panel.</Message>
	<Message id="INSURANCE4">This is really all there is to your insurance account. Close the window to end the tutorial</Message>
	<Message id="MARKETING1">Marketing is crucial in Software Inc. Your products simply won't sell without marketing.

You can start a marketing campaign by opening your release window and clicking the market button on the far right on the list of products.</Message>
	<Message id="MARKETING2">This is the marketing window. Marketing can be used for unreleased software or released software.

You start by picking what media outlets you want to use for your campaign. Using the interwebs is free but won't get as much attention as the rest. You can only reach the entire market using all the media outlets.

The more media outlets you choose, the more expensive the marketing will be.</Message>
	<Message id="MARKETING3">Now let's adjust the budget for your marketing campaign. The more money you spend, the greater effect your marketing will have.

The budget will be deducted from your account every day. The amount deducted depends on how successful the efforts have been that day, if no one works on marketing, you won't spend any money.

Press "Start campaign" to start your campaign.</Message>
	<Message id="MARKETING4">Your new marketing plan will appear as a work item on the right. Remember to assign a team or nothing will get done.

The work item will fill up as the day's marketing potential is being reached, which tells you how much of the budget has been used today.

Press "End" to end the tutorial.</Message>
	<Message id="PROJECT MANAGEMENT1">To enable project management open the team window</Message>
	<Message id="PROJECT MANAGEMENT2">With the team window open, scroll the team list all the way to the right and click "Automation" in the list, on the team you wish to enable project management for.</Message>
	<Message id="PROJECT MANAGEMENT3">Go over the software settings and check "Enable project management" when you are done.

If you don't select any teams for the various tasks, all tasks will be delegated to the current team, which will result in employee fatigue. The design phase is always delegated to the current team, so you should have designers ready.

Close the automation window to finish this tutorial.</Message>
	<Message id="RESEARCH1">Start the tutorial by pressing the "Research" button to bring up the design document.</Message>
	<Message id="RESEARCH2">If there is any available research you will see a list of software in this panel. You can click on a software type to see which features are available for research.

Press continue to advance.</Message>
	<Message id="RESEARCH3">This is a list of researchable features for the selected software type. You can see which features have already been researched and which are currently patented. Features will appear as they unlock through the years.

To research a feature, select it, click Research and pick the teams you want to conduct the research.</Message>
	<Message id="RESEARCH4">When you have researched a feature, all companies who use it in a product will have to pay royalties to you, based on how much the software sells.

Note that other companies might swoop in and steal the patent before you finish researching it and that patents eventually expire.</Message>
	<Message id="SERVER1">Open the server wiring interface by clicking the wire button.

In this mode you can connect or disconnect servers by clicking on a server and then on another server.

When servers are connected, one of them will be the main server for the group and will handle all wiring, all load you put on a server group will be distributed among every server in the group.</Message>
	<Message id="SERVER2">Try exiting build mode and open the server window.</Message>
	<Message id="SERVER3">From here you can manage your servers and check if they are overheating.

If you select a server group, you can see a list of all processes running on that server group. You can then redelegate those processes to other servers by pressing "Redelegate selected".</Message>
	<Message id="SERVER4">If you destroy a server group completely all processes will be unsupported, which can have major consequences.
If this happens you should click the "View unsupported processes" button and redelegate all processes to other servers.

Press End to finish the tutorial.</Message>
	<Message id="STAFF1">Begin by opening the staff window.</Message>
	<Message id="STAFF2">This is the staff window. At the top you will see a list of your currently employed staff, whether permanent or temporary.</Message>
	<Message id="STAFF3">With the buttons under "Permanent:" you can hire staff permanently to clean, fix your furniture, etc. You can see their salary by hovering over the buttons. They will show up once a day until you dismiss them.

You can change their working hours using the buttons in the list.</Message>
	<Message id="STAFF4">With the buttons under "Temporary:" you can hire staff temporarily. They will stay untill their job is done or until you dismiss them. Hovering over the buttons will show you their terms.

Press "End" to end the tutorial.</Message>
	<Message id="STOCKS1">In the upper right corner of the company window, you will see a list of stocks.

The first stock in the list is the company's own share, which you can buy if you have bought all other stocks in the list. Buying out a company will give you their IP and their patents.

When a company goes bankrupt, all its assets will go to the majority shareholder.</Message>
	<Message id="STOCKS2">When you own stock in another company, that company will pay dividends to you each month, which is the percentage you own in the company of their surplus for that month, divided by 24. You will also have to pay dividends to companies that own stock in your company, but it is an easy way to loan money.

Alternatively, you can buy the stock when it is cheap and sell it high, by trying to predict how the company will do, based on its history.</Message>
	<Message id="STOCKS3">In the bottom middle of the window you can see the companies patents. If you develop products with any of the feature listed, you will have to pay royalties to this company out of its profit. If you own stocks in the company, you do not have to pay royalites.</Message>
	<Message id="SUPPORT WORK1">When you release a new piece of software it will spawn a support work item. This work item will continually generate bugs that need to be fixed.

Make sure to quickly assign a team to this work item or it will affect your company's reputation.</Message>
	<Message id="SUPPORT WORK2">The work item will fill up as bugs are fixed, the blue line represents how many bugs have been reported so far. When the item is filled, the work is over and your software is bug free... In theory.</Message>
	<Message id="WELCOME1">欢迎来到Software Inc.

您可以通过点击并拖曳标题栏来移动此窗口。

点击“继续”来继续教程</Message>
	<Message id="WELCOME2">您可以通过WASD、按住CTRL和鼠标右键并拖曳或把你的鼠标移动到镜头边缘（在选项中打开画面边缘移动）来移动镜头。

您可以按住鼠标中键并移动鼠标或使用上、下、左、右箭头键来旋转镜头。

您可以使用鼠标滚轮或小键盘上的“+”、“-”键来拉近或拉远镜头。</Message>
	<Message id="WELCOME3">您可以按下ESC或画面右下角的齿轮图标来打开游戏选单，并在选项菜单中更改按键设置。</Message>
	<Message id="WELCOME4">这里是您公司当前的资金状况。</Message>
	<Message id="WELCOME5">这里的星星是您公司的声望，下面的数字是您公司的粉丝数。

鼠标悬浮在这里将会显示您公司在各软件市场的认可度。您需要通过在各软件市场卖出高质量的软件来提高您公司在该软件市场的认可度。更高的认可度将使您在该软件类别取得更多的销量。</Message>
	<Message id="WELCOME6">在这里您可以查看您公司的收支情况。

因为您的公司刚刚成立，这里不会有任何显示。如果您点击这里，将会显示一个经济的统计页面。</Message>
	<Message id="WELCOME7">您可以通过键盘上的0、1、2、3按钮来控制时间流动速度。</Message>
	<Message id="WELCOME8">在这里将会显示一些重要的通知。您可以把通知栏往下拉来查看一些旧的通知。

有些通知能够点击，这将把你的摄像机移动到与之关联的物体上。您可以通过右键点击来删除通知。</Message>
	<Message id="WELCOME9">这些按钮将帮助您控制您的公司。</Message>
	<Message id="WELCOME10">请记住：您能在任何时候通过选项重新开启您的教程。

当你准备好后，请打开“建造模式”来建造您的第一件办公室吧！</Message>
</Tutorial>

